$CEE_A2	MCM menu initialized
$CEE_A3	Expressions
$CEE_A4	Settings
$CEE_A5	Maintenance
$CEE_A51	Aroused Modifiers
$CEE_A6	Quick Eating
$CEE_A7	Slow Eating
$CEE_A8	Disabled
$CEE_A9	Vanilla - Snowing
$CEE_B1	Frostfall
$CEE_B2	Frostbite
$CEE_B3	Sunhelm Survival
$CEE_B4	Automatic
$CEE_B6	Conditional Expressions Extended. Version:
$CEE_B7	List of Expressions
$CEE_B8	Eating Expression
$CEE_B9	Less Dramatic Combat Expression
$CEE_C1	Random Idle Expressions
$CEE_C2	Cold Expression
$CEE_C3	Out of Stamina Expression
$CEE_C4	Cold Detection
$CEE_C5	In Pain Expression
$CEE_C6	Drunk Expression
$CEE_C7	This Is Good Skooma Expression
$CEE_C8	Embarrassed - No Clothes Expression
$CEE_C9	Sneaking Expression
$CEE_D1	Water/Torch Expression
$CEE_D2	Headache/Diseased
$CEE_D3	Trauma Expression
$CEE_D4	Dirty Expression
$CEE_D5	Aroused Expression
$CEE_D6	Settings
$CEE_D7	Breathing Sounds
$CEE_D8	Update interval
$CEE_D9	Expression Strength
$CEE_E1	Modifier Strength
$CEE_E2	Phoneme Strength
$CEE_E3	NPCs
$CEE_E4	NPCs Support
$CEE_E5	Update interval NPCs
$CEE_E6	Register NPCs
$CEE_E10	Register followers key
$CEE_E7	Maintenance
$CEE_E8	Update/Restart
$CEE_E9	Reset Current Expression:
$CEE_F1	Prepare to Uninstall
$CEE_F2	Verbose Notifications
$CEE_G1	Restarted to apply Automatic Cold Detection option!
$CEE_G2	Default expression restored - If in the middle of a face animation, expression will be restored once animation is finished.
$CEE_G3	Mod is now prepared to be uninstalled. Please, exit menu, save and uninstall. Keep in mind: It's never 100% safe to uninstall mods mid-game, always make back-ups of your saves before installing mods!
$CEE_G4	Please, exit menu. All functionalities will be restarted.
$CEE_G5	Restarted correctly!
$CEE_G6	Please, exit menu. Followers were registered
$CEE_G7	Followers support is disabled
$CEE_G8	Quick and slow refer to how fast your character starts chewing.\nDepending on your eating animation mod, one or the other will fit better.
$CEE_G9	This enables a more focused combat expression. Disabling this will revert back\n to the vanilla combat expression. Cannot be disabled during combat
$CEE_G10	When your character is idle, they will often have random subtle expressions.\n
$CEE_G11	Your character will react to being cold depending on your 'cold-manager' mod.\n
$CEE_G12	When out of Stamina, your character will be out of breath.
$CEE_G13	During low health, your character will be in pain/scared.
$CEE_G14	After drinking alcohol, your character will be 'happy' for 1 to 2 hours.
$CEE_G15	After taking skooma, your character will have \na random happier-than-usual expression for 1 to 2 hours.
$CEE_G16	When not at home, your character will have \nan embarrassed expression when wearing no clothes.
$CEE_G17	Your character will squint their eyes \nand look at their surroundings when sneaking.
$CEE_G18	Your character will squint their eyes \nwhen swimming or diving underwater.
$CEE_G19	If for some reason the face of your character \nis glitched, click here to reset it back to normal.
$CEE_G20	Clicking here will stop all functionalities of the mod.\nDo this ONLY if you are planning on uninstalling the mod right after.
$CEE_G21	The Automatic option scans your load order for frostfall or frostbite. Change this manually only\nif you have switched from one mod to another or want to use the vanilla detection method.
$CEE_G22	Clicking here will stop and restart the mod's functionalities.\nThis is useful if you have updated to a new version.
$CEE_G23	Your character will have a 'headache' look when almost out of mana.\nSame look will be applied when you have a disease.
$CEE_G24	When out of stamina, you can hear your character (quietly) breathing\n heavily until they recover half of their stamina. Enables trauma sounds as well
$CEE_G25	Your character will react to trauma or disease (painful subtle expressions).\n There's also a pain sound once in a while
$CEE_G26	Your character will react to dirt (disgusted subtle expressions).\n Integrated with Dirt&Blood,Keep it clean,Bathing in Skyrim
$CEE_G27	Your character will react to arousal (pleasure subtle expressions).\n Integrated with OSL Aroused
$CEE_G28	Verbose debug notifications. Shows what emotion is playing
$CEE_G29	Toggle  followers support
$CEE_G30	Clicking here will register new followers. Followers are also registered when game is loaded.
$CEE_G31	Update period for followers expressions
$CEE_G32	Update period for long term conditions checking. Set to 0 if you want to disable them
$CEE_G33	Expression strength - 1 means default unmodified
$CEE_G34	Modifier strength - 1 means default unmodified
$CEE_G35	Phoneme strength - 1 means default unmodified
$CEE_E11	Keep expressions during dialogue
$CEE_G36	You and your followers keep reacting through a conversation, instead of the mod standing down for all of it. Whoever is actually speaking keeps their mouth: your character keeps the rest of the face, and a talking NPC is left alone until their line ends. Worth turning on with a player voice mod or a dialogue camera.
$CEE_F3	    ... also for followers
$CEE_G37	Followers keep reacting through a conversation too. A talking NPC is never written over - their line already animates their whole face - so expressions land in the gaps, while you read the topic list. Turn this off if NPC faces look wrong between lines: their own dialogue mood is what gets replaced.
