$CHMCMPageName01	Main
$CHMCMPageName02	Horses
$CHMCMPageName03	Followers
$CHMCMPageName04	Auto Loot
$CHMCMPageName05	Horse Charge
$CHMCMEquipmentName00	 UNAVAILABLE 
$CHMCMEquipmentName01	 Original Equipment 
$CHMCMEquipmentName02	 Bareback 
$CHMCMEquipmentName03	 Nordic Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName04	 Imperial Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName05	 Dark Brotherhood Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName06	 Traveler Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName07	 Bard Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName08	 Hunter Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName09	 Knight Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName10	 Big Game Hunter Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName11	 Dawnguard Saddle 
$CHMCMEquipmentName12	 Leather Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName13	 Nordic Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName14	 Dwemer Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName15	 Ebony Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName16	 Daedric Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName17	 Dragonbone Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName18	 Elthrai Armor 
$CHMCMEquipmentName19	 Sethai Armor 
$CHMCMSkinName01	 Random 
$CHMCMSkinName02	 Black 
$CHMCMSkinName03	 Black & White 
$CHMCMSkinName04	 Brown 
$CHMCMSkinName05	 Grey 
$CHMCMSkinName06	 Palomino 
$CHMCMPresetName01	Chip
$CHMCMPresetName02	Flop
$CHMCMPresetName03	Top
$CHMCMPresetName04	Punch
$CHMCMPresetName05	Drive
$CHMCMQuestErrorMsg	Convenient Horses main quest is not running.\n\nIt is recommended that you exit all menus and start it via console (StartQuest CH) before proceeding with configuration.
$CHMCMButtonOK	OK
$CHMCMValueInt	{0}
$CHMCMValueMS	{0} milliseconds
$CHMCMValueFT	{0} feet
$CHMCMValueS	{0} seconds
$CHMCMValueGold	{0} gold
$CHMCMValueVW	{0} v/w
$CHMCMValuePct	{0}%
$CHMCMValueDeg	{0}°
$CHMCMStateInvalid	Invalid Entry
$CHMCMStateShown	Shown
$CHMCMStateHidden	Hidden
$CHMCMStateRunning	Running
$CHMCMStateStopped	Stopped
$CHMCMStateMultiTap	Multi Tap
$CHMCMStateBoundKey	Bound Key
$CHMCMStateNever	Never
$CHMCMStateCombat	Combat
$CHMCMStateAlways	Always
$CHMCMStateSmart	Smart
$CHMCMStateLocal	Local
$CHMCMStateTravel	Travel
$CHMCMStateRemote	Remote
$CHMCMStateAbsolute	Absolute
$CHMCMStatePerFollower	Per Follower
$CHMCMStateGlobal	Global
$CHMCMStateDisabled	Disabled
$CHMCMStateBasic	Basic
$CHMCMStateAdvanced	Advanced
$CHMCMStateIgnore	Ignore
$CHMCMStateLoot	Loot
$CHMCMStateStash	Stash
$CHMCMStateRecoverOn	Recover (Queued)
$CHMCMStateRecoverOff	Do Not Recover
$CHMCMStateFactionUpdateOn	Update (Queued)
$CHMCMStateFactionUpdateOff	Do Not Update
$CHMCMStateFactionNeutral	Neutral
$CHMCMStateFactionFriendly	Friendly
$CHMCMStateProtOff	No Protection
$CHMCMStateProtEssential	Essential
$CHMCMStateProtInvulnerable	Invulnerable
$CHMCMStateBehaviorCowardly	Cowardly
$CHMCMStateBehaviorFoolhardy	Foolhardy
$CHMCMStateDist30	Short (30 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist45	Medium (45 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist60	Long (60 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist56	Short (56 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist112	Medium (112 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist168	Long (168 feet)
$CHMCMStateDist225	Very Long (225 feet)
$CHMCMTxtGeneral	General
$CHMCMTxtPreferences	Preferences
$CHMCMTxtFactionRelations	Faction Relations
$CHMCMTxtMisc	Miscellaneous
$CHMCMTxtMultiTap	Multi Tap Settings
$CHMCMTxtBoundKey	Bound Key Settings
$CHMCMTxtHorseBonus	Horse Attribute Bonuses
$CHMCMTxtHorseProtection	Horse Protection
$CHMCMTxtMountedCombat	Mounted Combat
$CHMCMTxtWeightLimit	Weight Limit
$CHMCMTxtHorseInventory	Horse Inventory
$CHMCMTxtHorseAI	Horse AI
$CHMCMTxtHorseCall	Horse Call Settings
$CHMCMTxtHorseRiding	Horse Riding
$CHMCMTxtHorseCalling	Horse Calling
$CHMCMTxtHorseSkins	Horse Skins
$CHMCMTxtHorseEquipment	Horse Equipment
$CHMCMTxtFeatures	Features
$CHMCMTxtLootRules	Advanced Loot Rules
$CHMCMTxtControlMode	Control Mode
$CHMCMTxtFactionRelationsMode	Horse Faction Relations
$CHMCMTxtFactionRelationsUpdate	Update Relations
$CHMCMTxtConfigPower	Configuration Power
$CHMCMTxtScriptLatency	Gameplay Script Latency Test
$CHMCMTxtInventoryRecovery	Horse Inventory Recovery
$CHMCMTxtAnimations	Follow Toggle & Whistle Animations
$CHMCMTxtCameraFix	Mounted Combat Camera Auto-Correction
$CHMCMTxtHorseTracking	Disable Game's Horse Tracking
$CHMCMTxtLearnWhistleOverride	Horse Whistle Quest Override
$CHMCMTxtMTDelay	Multi Tap Delay
$CHMCMTxtMTCombatOverride	Combat Override
$CHMCMTxtMTFastDismount	Fast Dismount
$CHMCMTxtBKInventoryAccess	Inventory Access Mode
$CHMCMTxtBKConsolidate	Consolidate Talk/Loot/Harvest
$CHMCMTxtBKKeyTalk	Talk/Loot Key
$CHMCMTxtBKKeyHarvest	Harvest Ingredient Key
$CHMCMTxtBKKeyDismount	Fast Dismount Key
$CHMCMTxtBKKeyInventory	Horse Inventory Key
$CHMCMTxtBKKeySpecial	Follow Toggle Key
$CHMCMTxtBonusHealth	Health Bonus
$CHMCMTxtBonusStamina	Stamina Bonus
$CHMCMTxtBonusSpeed	Speed Bonus
$CHMCMTxtProtectionMode	Protection Mode
$CHMCMTxtCombatBehavior	Combat Behavior
$CHMCMTxtHorseFollow	Horse Follow
$CHMCMTxtFollowMode	Follow Mode
$CHMCMTxtFollowDist	Follow Distance
$CHMCMTxtFormation	Horse Call Delta Formation
$CHMCMTxtScreenFade	Horse Call Screen Fade
$CHMCMTxtFollowersHorses	Followers' Horses
$CHMCMTxtPreferRiding	Prefer Riding
$CHMCMTxtAutoRetaliate	Auto Retaliate
$CHMCMTxtCombatEscape	Combat Escape
$CHMCMTxtDeferredDismount	Deferred Dismount
$CHMCMTxtDeferRadius	- Zone Radius
$CHMCMTxtDeferTime	- Time
$CHMCMTxtHorseRecall	Horse Recall
$CHMCMTxtCallDist	Call Distance
$CHMCMTxtMCDamage	Mounted Combat Damage
$CHMCMTxtSkinSelection	Skin Selection
$CHMCMTxtGlobalSkin	Global Skin
$CHMCMTxtEquipmentSelection	Equipment Selection
$CHMCMTxtGlobalEquipment	Global Equipment
$CHMCMTxtDynamicSpeed	Dynamic Speed
$CHMCMTxtAutoLootMode	Auto Loot Mode
$CHMCMTxtEquipment	Equipment
$CHMCMTxtEquipmentEnchOnly	- Enchanted Only
$CHMCMTxtEquipmentMinVW	- Minimum Gold Per Weight
$CHMCMTxtSpellTomes	Spell Tomes
$CHMCMTxtSpellTomesUnknownOnly	- Unknown Only
$CHMCMTxtBooks	Books
$CHMCMTxtBooksMinValue	- Minimum Value
$CHMCMTxtScrolls	Magical Scrolls
$CHMCMTxtRecipes	Alchemy Recipes
$CHMCMTxtHides	Animal Hides
$CHMCMTxtIngots	Ore & Ingots
$CHMCMTxtIngredients	Ingredients
$CHMCMTxtPotions	Potions
$CHMCMTxtPoisons	Poisons
$CHMCMTxtFood	Food & Drinks
$CHMCMTxtSoulGems	Soul Gems
$CHMCMTxtJewels	Precious Gems
$CHMCMTxtAmmo	Ammo
$CHMCMTxtLight	Torches
$CHMCMTxtKeys	Keys
$CHMCMTxtHorseCharge	Horse Charge
$CHMCMTxtImpactPrecog	Impact Precognition
$CHMCMTxtImpactSFX	Impact Sound Effect
$CHMCMTxtDamageBase	Damage Base
$CHMCMTxtDamageHealthPercent	Damage Health Percentage
$CHMCMTxtStaminaCostPercent	Stamina Cost Percentage
$CHMCMTxtPhysicsSimulator	Physics Simulator
$CHMCMTxtLoadPreset	Load Preset
$CHMCMTxtAngleTolerance	Heading Angle Tolerance
$CHMCMTxtForceDissipation	Heading Force Dissipation
$CHMCMTxtForceAmount	Push Force Amount
$CHMCMTxtElevationAngle	Angle of Elevation
$CHMCMTxtFeedbackDuration	Speed Penalty Duration
$CHMCMTxtFeedbackAmount	Speed Penalty Amount
$CHMCMInfoControlModeBK	Bound Key Mode: Use defined keys for each of the following features (Talk/Loot, Harvest, Fast Dismount, Inventory and Follow Toggle). Multi Tap mode will be forced if SKSE not found.
$CHMCMInfoControlModeMT	Multi Tap Mode: Target horse and press [Activate] button specific number of times (Single Tap - Mount/Dismount, Dismounted Double Tap - Inventory, Dismounted Triple Tap - Follow Toggle, Mounted Multi Tap - Talk/Loot/Harvest).
$CHMCMInfoFactionRelationsMode	Friendly (mod default) - Horse will neither attack nor get attacked by anyone who is a member of any known faction.\nNeutral (game default) - Horse becomes a valid target for aggressive actors and might participate in combat.
$CHMCMInfoFactionRelationsUpdate	Once updated, faction relations are saved with the game.\nFactions relations are automatically queued for an update if supported mod or DLC containing new factions is detected.
$CHMCMInfoConfigPower	Whether to display old configuration power in magic menu. If left hidden it will be automatically shown once game is loaded without MCM capabilities.
$CHMCMInfoLearnWhistleOverride	Suspends the horse whistle learning quest and grants the horse whistle power.\nDoes not have effect if horse whistle power has already been obtained by completing the quest.
$CHMCMInfoScriptLatency	Measure script latency as you play and display notification every few seconds. Ideally latency should stay around 50 ms and never go above 100 ms. Wrong results caused by menu mode should be ignored.
$CHMCMInfoInventoryRecovery	If queued for recovery any items stored in horse inventory will be automatically trasnfered to the player when configuration is closed.
$CHMCMInfoInventoryWeightLimit	Horse inventory storage limit will not prevent from using quick transfer functions or directly stashing items via advanced auto loot. Browsing limited inventory will preserve but not show item ownership.\nSet to 0 for unlimited storage.
$CHMCMInfoAnimations	Enable or disable horse whistle and follow toggle animations.
$CHMCMInfoCameraFix	Enable or disable mounted combat horse camera position auto correction. Camera bug occurs when follower mounts the horse or sheathes the weapon after mounted combat because game does not make difference between player and NPCs both triggering same animation events.
$CHMCMInfoHorseTracking	Enable to prevent horse from being moved on fast travel. This feature also prevents game from keeping track of player's last ridden horse when dismounted which in turn might affect mods that rely on game's horse tracking system. Does not apply to summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoMTDelay	Time to wait before interpreting the number of [Activate] button taps in Multi Tap Mode. Lower number gives faster response time at cost of accuracy. Higher number gives more accuracy at cost of response time.
$CHMCMInfoMTCombatOverride	Enable to bypass multi-tap processing while in combat to maximize mount/dismount response time.
$CHMCMInfoMTDismountMode	When should fast dismounting be used instead of a standard dismounting.
$CHMCMInfoBKInventoryLocal	Local: Restrict inventory access so it can be opened only when near the horse.
$CHMCMInfoBKInventoryTravel	Travel: If not near the horse you can hold down inventory key to fast travel to the horse, open inventory and then travel back to initial position. Travel access can only be used from rideable zones, major cities, shops, player houses, guild houses, castles and inns.
$CHMCMInfoBKInventoryRemote	Remote: Gives instant inventory access regardless of distance. Remote access can only be used from rideable zones, major cities, shops, player houses, guild houses, castles and inns.
$CHMCMInfoBKInventoryAbsolute	Absolute: Gives instant inventory access regardless of all conditions.
$CHMCMInfoBKConsolidate	Whether to use Talk/Loot key to perform harvesting if no actors have been found.
$CHMCMInfoBKKeyTalk	Which key to use to talk to people or loot dead bodies from a horseback.\nUnbind the key by restoring to default.
$CHMCMInfoBKKeyHarvest	Which key to use to harvest ingredients from a horseback.\nUnbind the key by restoring to default.
$CHMCMInfoBKKeyDismount	Which key to use to fast dismount.\nUnbind the key by restoring to default.
$CHMCMInfoBKKeyInventory	Which key to use for horse inventory access.\nUnbind the key by restoring to default.
$CHMCMInfoBKKeySpecial	Which key to use to toggle horse follow.\nUnbind the key by restoring to default.
$CHMCMInfoHorseEquipmentMode	Armored horses do not have any additional protection (cosmetic feature) and equipment is automatically transferred when switching to a new horse.
$CHMCMInfoBonusHealth	Increase health of player's current horse. Does not apply to summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoBonusStamina	Increase stamina of player's current horse. Does not apply to summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoBonusSpeed	Increase movement speed of player's current horse and all followers' horses. Also applies to summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoHorseProtOff	Player's current horse is vulnerable and may die.
$CHMCMInfoHorseProtEssential	Player's current horse is essential and cannot die when its health is depleted.
$CHMCMInfoHorseProtInvulnerable	Player's current horse is invulnerable and does not lose health or stamina, allowing it to sprint indefinitely.
$CHMCMInfoBehaviorCowardly	Cowardly horse will run away from threats. Best paired with faction relations set to Friendly. Behavior changes apply only to player's current horse excluding summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoBehaviorFoolhardy	Foolhardy horse will always fight back and deal more damage than usual. Best paired with faction relations set to Neutral. Behavior changes apply only to player's current horse excluding summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoHorseFollow	Enable or disable horses following their owners. Can also be toggled in game with related controls. Does not apply to summoned horses.
$CHMCMInfoHorseFollowMode	Smart follow will cause horses to stop following temporarily if player is sneaking or in certain locations.
$CHMCMInfoHorseFollowDist	Player's horse will try to maintain specific distance when following.\n1 foot = 21.3 game units or 0.3 meters.
$CHMCMInfoFormation	Followers will form a delta formation with the player after using group Horse Call.
$CHMCMInfoScreenFade	Screen will fade to black for few seconds to hide teleportation effects when using Horse Call.
$CHMCMInfoFollowersHorses	Convenient Horses can provide followers with their own horses and control their riding behavior.\nSupported follower mods: Extensible Follower Framework, Ultimate Follower Overhaul and Amazing Follower Tweaks. Maximum 15 horses.
$CHMCMInfoPreferRiding	Followers will ride even if player is not riding. Can also be toggled by talking to any of the followers.
$CHMCMInfoAutoRetaliate	Followers will engage in combat even if player is riding with weapons sheathed and will not break from combat until it completes.
$CHMCMInfoCombatEscape	Followers will break from combat and mount the horse if player is riding with weapons sheathed.
$CHMCMInfoDeferredDismount	If enabled, followers will not dismount until player leaves defer zone or defer time runs out.\nUseful when dismounting to interact with the environment and want followers to stay mounted.\nDoes not work in combat.
$CHMCMInfoDeferRadius	How far player needs to move away after dismounting before followers decide to dismount themselves.\n1 foot = 21.3 game units or 0.3 meters.
$CHMCMInfoDeferTime	How long should followers wait for player to leave defer zone before dismounting.\nSet to 0 to wait indefinitely.
$CHMCMInfoHorseRecall	Followers' horses will be recalled (teleported out of existence) when not being ridden and followers will always use Horse Call when they want to ride.
$CHMCMInfoCallDist	Followers will use Horse Call if horses are past the certain distance threshold, otherwise followers will normally run toward their horses to mount them.\n1 foot = 21.3 game units or 0.3 meters.
$CHMCMInfoMountedCombat	Allows followers to engage in melee mounted combat. Weapons are auto-provided for the duration.
$CHMCMInfoMCdamage	Damage is scaled with player level and takes into account follower's related weapon skills, skill enchants and buffs. You may control the final damage percentage.
$CHMCMInfoSkinSelection	Whether to use global skin for all followers' horses or set individually by talking to each follower.
$CHMCMInfoGlobalSkin	All followers' horses will be of selected type.
$CHMCMInfoEquipmentSelection	Whether to use global equipment for all followers' horses or set individually by talking to each follower.
$CHMCMInfoGlobalEquipment	All followers' horses will be equipped with selected item.
$CHMCMInfoDynamicSpeed	Dynamic speed scales followers' riding speed with distance allowing them to catch up with the player more easily.\nSpeed starts to increase when 1200 game units away from the player with formula:\n(distance-1200)^0.5 resulting in speed percentage (e.g. if distance=3700 then followers ride 50% faster).
$CHMCMInfoAutoLoot	Slain enemies will have their inventory opened automatically (Basic) or specific items looted according to defined rules (Advanced). Gold and lockpicks will always be looted in advanced mode.\nAuto loot works only in mounted combat with maximum range of 100 feet.
$CHMCMInfoIngredients	Includes all alchemical ingredients.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoHides	Includes all tanning materials.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoIngots	Includes all ore and ingots.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoPotions	Includes all beneficial potions.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoPoisons	Includes all poisons.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoSpellTomes	Includes all spell tomes.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoSpellTomesUnknownOnly	If enabled, only spell tomes that teach unknown spells will be included.
$CHMCMInfoBooks	Includes all books.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoBooksMinValue	Books cheaper than this value will be ignored.\nBooks that teach skills usually have cost of 50 gold or more.
$CHMCMInfoLight	Includes all carriable light sources.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoFood	Includes all meat, food and beverage.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoRecipes	Includes all alchemy recipes that are not currently owned.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoScrolls	Includes all magical scrolls.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoSoulGems	Includes all empty and filled soul gems.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoJewels	Includes all jewels.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoKeys	Includes all keys that are not currently owned.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoAmmo	Includes all arrows and bolts.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoEquipment	Includes all armor, clothing, jewelry and weapons.\nIt can be ignored, looted or stashed directly to a horse inventory.\nIf item is stashed it will display asterisk symbol in notification.
$CHMCMInfoEquipmentEnchOnly	If enabled, only magical equipment will be included.
$CHMCMInfoEquipmentMinVW	Equipment with value to weight ratio lower than this will be ignored.\nFor example if item has 10 weight and costs 250 gold it will only be included if this value is set to 25 or lower.
$CHMCMInfoHorseCharge	Enable or disable mounted combat horse charge feature.\nSprinting while in mounted combat will allow horse to knock targets it runs into.
$CHMCMInfoHCImpactPrecog	Horse charge collision calculations do not run in sync with frame rates but it is possible to precognize the moment of impact and execute hit event prematurely. Decrease if targets are being hit by invisible wall. Increase if hit is never occuring or is being delayed.
$CHMCMInfoHCDamageBase	Fixed amount of physical damage before other modifiers.\nKnocking targets with horse charge is not considered an assault if total damage is zero.
$CHMCMInfoHCDamagePercent	Physical damage as a percentage of target's maximum health before other modifiers.\nKnocking targets with horse charge is not considered an assault if total damage is zero.
$CHMCMInfoHCStaminaCost	For each target struck horse loses a percentage of its maximum stamina.
$CHMCMInfoHCSFXMode	Switch between available impact sound effects.
$CHMCMInfoHCLoadPreset	Load predefined set of physics simulator parameters.
$CHMCMInfoHCAngleTolerance	Ignore target if angle between horse heading direction and target is greater than this value.
$CHMCMInfoHCForceDissipation	Linear loss of the force over the angle of tolerance. If set to zero, force is at its maximum in all directions.\nIf greater than zero, magnitude of push force, damage, stamina cost and speed penalty is reduced up to this amount depending on the heading angle at the moment of impact.
$CHMCMInfoHCPushForce	Push force is scaled with horse speed.\nBy changing this value you can control the amount of force that is used to push targets away.
$CHMCMInfoHCElevationAngle	Controls vertical angle of attack.\nIncrease to send targets flying or reduce to make them slide over the ground.
$CHMCMInfoHCSlowTime	Simulate recoil by slowing the horse temporarily at the moment of collision.
$CHMCMInfoHCSlowPercent	How much to reduce horse speed on a per target basis.